i have
no idea what i'm doing i'll be honest
with you straight off the bat i have
been experimenting with the mycelium
resistance base here it is the source
block and i have been making
a meeting room which is the center of
the base the issue is i don't really
know what i'm doing with the rest of
this space
at all
we have our base design plan which is
source block room done meeting room done
but then we need the lab testing
facility storage room and everything
else and there's a mysterious machine
that etho wants to make and i didn't
really understand what it is but he told
me some space that is needed so i really
need to just crack on and get this thing
properly designed but apart from this
central piece with all the meeting
chairs and such i'm not really sure what
i need to do so
i think actually what we're going to do
is kick off this episode by
making the mycelium resistance
base which is easier said than done
when you don't know what you're doing so
let's just get straight into it and make
at least what we can
[Music]
check it out the mycelium resistance
base i totally winged this design
and it's come out pretty awesome in my
opinion i accidentally made it shaped
like a mushroom which is pretty on point
it ended up being about a five or six
hour build but i'm actually getting
close to completion i've created a bunch
of corridors and potential rooms where
stuff is going to be now that this room
is done i want to call a meeting of
everyone
and on here i think what i'm going to do
is give everyone a title so they know
what to do
without too much direction in order to
keep everyone anonymous because the
mycelium resistance members are not
known this is the new face of the
resistance
b b-dubs
and his smiley big-eyed face
everyone gets their own b-dubs head you
wear this on official duty
and they'll never see who it is nope
minecraft doesn't have usernames above
the head just faces
so we got etho
head of shenanigans
we got impulse impulse is going to be
head of diversionary tactics xp crafted
head of recruitment granddog head of
r head of r and d it's not research and
development it's it's it's head of ren
and dog so that is the team oh and then
there's me brian mother spore so
everyone has their job and then i'm
going to try and help out everyone as
well as being like the builder i suppose
i've already done most of my job by
making this room but basically i'm
hoping that etho will make his room the
shenanigans room impulse will make some
diversionary stuff like we need a
laboratory like everyone has their own
thing to do so i'm gonna keep these for
the meeting later on and let all the
members know that we need to have a
meeting about our plan
for spreading mycelium look the plan's
right here farm mycelium spread the
spores we built the base
now we've got to fire mycelium this
ended up being such a large project that
i've ended up spending like two days on
it so for now we're gonna leave this
place and we'll be back when everyone
else is ready
so what i think we should do
is get ourselves
back on the mystery box money making
scheme because this thing has been
actually generating most of my profits
the hermits will buy stuff from the
barge as and when they need the real way
to make
what i'm i'm invisible again
whoa
what the
heck green
no green green
no green
i don't like this
the real way to make stonks on this
server is to sell them things
i'm invisible and i can see b-dubs in
the background the real way to make
stonks on this server is to sell them
stuff they don't need that's how you
make real money and the only way to do
that is by wrapping it in an enigma so
i'm gonna come up with four different
treasure hunts
all on the mystery barge box and they're
going to be even more expensive every
time i sell out i make new barge mystery
boxes i up the price and i make them
more insane that's probably the most
suspicious behavior i've ever seen
what are they up to i bet better turn
around and put on my face of the
resistance boom
it's like looking in a handsome mirror
he's doing he's doing the wiggle dancer
friendship
wiggle wiggle wiggle yeah there we go
we're the same person
whoa
what on earth
is this how have i not seen this the
oh there's x on top of it and corrales
thank thank goodness i'm wearing my
disguise
it's the it's the hep it's it's the
hermit environmental protection agency
it's it's here
i thought they're gonna be cool from now
on yep
what is going on they're up to no good
that is a magnificent building oh my
goodness i just finished our
headquarters
and the hip have gone ahead and they've
made something
probably equally as good maybe even a
little bit better actually that kind of
is better than my base look the
resistance has to be underground it's
difficult to make stuff underground but
anyway let's focus for a sec what is
that is sus
there is so many sus
an imposter
there is an imp
is an imposter among us you saw that i
saw i saw with my own
two big eyes a member of the resistance
having a casual encounter oh yeah i also
placed some mycelium anyway let's focus
and get ourselves
these mystery barge boxes underway
also xp did look kind of afk but that's
still kind of sus so this time around
i'm gonna have all the barge boxes be
overvalued they will all be worth more
than a hundred diamonds worth of value
which is what i'm gonna sell them for if
you bought all this at the shopping
district it would cost you 46 diamonds
so there are four different treasure
hunts that we're gonna make but i'm only
gonna show one on camera as i don't want
to spoil every single one this box alone
is worth 50 diamonds if you count all
the tnt that's most of the value in here
but then you got the woods you got the
carrots you got two boxes of rockets and
a beacon so this will be the prize of
the first treasure hunt we're doing and
it's a general prize this is not
specific to any one thing this is a
general prize and it's pretty decent the
total value
140 diamonds that's not including the
shulker boxes so it may even be a little
bit more it's around 150 and so now we
have to go and bury this so as with the
last treasure hunt what we're gonna do
is rename
our initial box so this is what they'll
get and we need to rename this head to
give them the first clue
follow the gaze of the broken face
that's the broken face
dude
it's happening again there's straight up
some collusion going on here tell me
this doesn't look sus i see you so we
follow the gaze of the broken face
now his eyes are looking
down here so if i was following it i'd
look somewhere down
here i mean if that face isn't looking
at me and then i i don't know so down
here is what we're gonna do and then we
leave the next clue but i need to know
where the next clue leads so i've got
this alone in his own world he is happy
visit the shopping district to find the
treasure mappy look
rhyming is not my strong suit i always
make puns and rhymes by accident when i
do it on purpose i end up with happy and
mappy don't judge me okay this stuff is
hard so of course i mean alone in his
own world he is happy i'm talking about
our unvisited friend
grumbot oh my goodness i forgot how
happy he looks now we go inside here
and the next treasure map as it says is
visit the shopping district to find the
treasure mappy now i don't think anyone
would ever have a reason to enter here
other than this clue so the shopping
district which is still mycelium this is
how it should be
is over here so you have to visit the
shopping district
where mumbo is where mumbo is still
there
and i'm going to put the treasure map
here
so basically for this
this thing is mainly a series of clues
so they'll come down here
they'll take this and they'll see your
next clue so this is only a two-stage
treasure hunt so far now i need to make
a map
it's still going on
this is so sus this is very very sus
so now i need to make an empty map and
it needs to be somewhere super
recognizable if you're gonna identify it
from a map so i'm thinking one of the
most identifiable builds is mumbo's base
because of its massive geometric shape
so if i go here and i turn this into a
map
we end up with this now if i go down
here and build an x
that's not as red as i'd like but it's
there
and i bury
the next clue
under here
of course i need to lock this map so
that the x remains there so you kind of
get the idea that these things take a
really long time to set up so i really
hope the hermits enjoy them so now that
this map is locked even if i remove this
the x will stay here
and this is the map that goes in
grumbot's virtual reality and then in
here we put the next clue i think this
will have to be the final clue for this
one
i have a really good idea but i think it
might be too difficult i'm going to just
call this
chest
ception
chest section
that's the clue
it's not a joke that is the clue
so we put the treasure map here for them
to find and hopefully take and if you
haven't worked it out chest ception
there is only one big chest on the
server
and that is
good old good times with mayor the chest
monster so if we go in here we hide
ourselves a chest bada bing bada boom
all of the rewards go in here
of course there is a chance that someone
will find this just because they're
hunting for decked out keys and now you
get the idea
about these what is going on everything
is so suspicious today literally
everyone is acting so weird
including me
so here is the first completed one so
i've renamed this to barge box treasure
hunt i would say it's medium it's not
it's not easy this one but it's not
ridiculously difficult so
there we go the first treasure hunt is
done now the other ones are all gonna
have to be done off camera because i
just totally explained and ruined that
entire one although the chances are this
will probably be sold before i even get
to upload this video so you probably
can't spoil it that much mystery box
treasure hunts 100 diamonds each that's
quite a lot of diamonds not gonna lie
that is a lot of diamonds but
it's a lot of fun and you do get a
really cool reward at the end of it
value is always over what you pay good
luck so now i've got three more to make
off camera and we'll see how the hermits
take them this has been my biggest money
making scheme on the server so far
free pumpkins for halloween one box per
person
yes please i'm gonna use that
where are they
ah
there it is
scary flying bat things
so annoying
yeah gonna use all of these pumpkins to
trade with my villagers this is my this
is my xp farm and has been for a while
so
time to make
more mystery barge boxes and the most
difficult of which will get the ultimate
prize of the netherite block included in
their prize pool and remember that is
worth 250
diamonds on its own these things are
ridiculous
so someone is going to make a whole lot
of diamonds but i'm not going to make it
easy for them so good luck to everyone
that is going to try and win a mystery
bargebox treasure hunt i probably need a
better name for that because that is a
mouthful so off camera we go to put
these together uh as usual that took a
lot longer than i thought and i tried to
get a little bit more creative with some
of them i would say that about three of
these boxes involve
mainly finding books and solving a
riddle going to another place however a
couple of them have something a little
bit more interesting involved in them
but as you can see five treasure hunts
are all completed
and they are very very expensive 100
diamonds each but that's the price you
gotta pay
for a little game like this and we've
also got a pesky bird now you may notice
there's another pesky bird in the
background now this is a very special
box i am reserved specifically for scar
okay and a little bit of a a spoiler
it says behind the beard of your best
house so i think scar will get that
pretty quickly however
his one is especially for him and
there's no payment required because of a
deal
that i made with scar
i made a deal to purchase a whole lot of
shulker shells from him and i did a part
payment in diamonds and he wanted an iou
from green
which i said absolutely not that's the
worst idea ever if if a hermit asks you
for an iou you don't do it that can come
back to haunt you so instead he said he
wanted a unique treasure hunt that i was
making so
i made one specifically for scar
and it's gonna it's gonna be quite funny
so i look forward to seeing how that all
goes down so
we've got an awful lot done today we
have continued our money-making barge
box scheme and now since i found a
decked-out box i would like to go and do
another run i've had some pretty
terrible luck in this game but we're
going to try
and actually get out of here with a
proper token okay i've got my decked out
box i've got myself a key i've actually
got two keys so let's go okay the decked
out box with all my cards goes in i
haven't got very good cards and we are
ready to
go right let's just go straight for the
compass this time and let's play it safe
oh be sense
nothing nearby
oh okay so we need to head this
direction
oh man
i hate this
okay we're across okay okay okay
we got this
oh is this it
there we go there we go we got the loot
box token okay if we take the long way
round we can do a little bit of
exploring actually i hear a ravager
there so i say we just go back the way
we came and we claim we just claim the
loot
super easy
not too much exploring
okay this is gonna be an easy run easy
run
dude okay
loot box token acquired
i know i didn't go for any of the extra
hidden stuff
but i really needed a win
i really needed this win what did we get
a b set b set a unique b that's amazing
we have a b set we have two b set
commons we have a villagers set which i
don't need let's do one more run
we just gotta wait for the doors to
close again
i totally forgot to end the game oh my
bad i totally forgot to end the game the
doors are closed round two maybe this
time we can be a little bit
more adventurous now that we got a win
under our belt it's time to go this
direction again
is it here
no okay we gotta go across the worst
thing ever again
okay once you know how to do this it's
not too bad
is it raining outside
okay let's be careful
oh
the stealth the stealth is really
helping me out here
i hear no ravages
so far so good gold room this has got to
be it right
there it is there it is loot box token
well that was super easy
okay we might as well
make our way round and try and find
ourselves a few secrets
like that
boom
empty barrel
and the soul flame thing is not open
that is a crying shame
okay
unfortunately oh wait you could totally
just open this from here
oh man
did he see me
fortunately i don't think the ravager
saw me
okay
so i know a few secret rooms but not not
a huge amount of them and i very rarely
find soul flames
oh that was a ravager
oh my goodness that is the spookiest
thing oh he saw me he saw me okay i
think it's time to leave
again it was a little bit easier to get
this token
and i didn't find any
any extra coins but honestly
sometimes after a few losses i think
it's time we just take take the wins on
this i need some artifacts under my belt
okay not the most exciting decked out
runs in the world
but we got
our reward
one of these loot 38
let's see what we got
oh wow
we got a lot of decked out coins this
time
but unfortunately
we got nothing rare or unique ocean set
end set villager set
actually i've got a repeat unfortunately
i don't think there's a lot i can do
with these
none of these are useful well it wasn't
a complete bust we got some coins we got
out of there alive but we didn't have
the guts
to go deep into the dungeon looking for
prizes every time i've done that it's
ended extremely badly but oh my goodness
i saw this earlier and i didn't know
what to say
rip throne
the diamond throne has gone
and
it's actually partly because of me
remember when i made the hermit
challenges for iska mumbo well they went
and replaced the diamond throne with
mycelium and obviously scars gotten rid
of the mycelium throne and everyone's
putting in their condolences so i think
we'll do the same
put in that
lay down some flowers for the throne i'm
sure it will be back i'm sure like mumbo
wouldn't have actually taken it he's
probably just hidden it away somewhere
so it should be back
in no time at all but that's quite funny
you tasted so good so that is all for
today's episode i really do hope you
enjoyed the episode we did a lot today
what is going on here
that is very strange
and we have done an awful lot today
making the mycelium headquarters which
took up most of my day making the
treasure hunt boxes which is very
exciting for the hermits that want to
pay me lots of diamonds
and of course we got some decked out
runs today overall i'd say it's been a
pretty productive episode we got a lot
done and i'm very excited to see where
this mycelium turf war keeps on going so
that is all i hope you enjoy the video
and don't forget
subscribe maybe because you know last
time i asked you guys to subscribe i got
like 10 000 subscribers in a day which
is kind of cool so if you haven't
subscribed please do and i want to thank
you all again for watching i'll see you
in the next episode good bye